Guide to the Charles Hamm Recordings, 1857-1999 HAMM.2005
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Recordings on LP, 1
  - Popular, 1871-1999; IX.
    - Steely Dan: Pretzel Logic, 1974 (Record HAMM POP 0312)
      This album includes Rikki don't lose that number -- Night by night -- Any major dude will tell you -- Barrytown -- East St. Louis Toodle-oo -- Parker's band -- Through with buzz -- Pretzel logic -- With a gun -- Charlie freak -- Monkey in your soul.
    - Stephen Stills, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0313)
      This album includes Love the one you are with (3:03) -- Do for the others (2:52) -- Church (Part of Someone) (4:05) -- Old times good times (3:38) -- Go back home (5:56) -- Sit yourself down (3:05) -- To a flame (3:10) -- Black Queen (5:28) -- Cherokee (3:25) -- We are not helpless (4:17).
    - Stephen Stills: Manassas, 1972 (Record HAMM POP 0314)
      This album includes The raven: Song of love; Rock & roll crazies; Cuban bluegrass; Jet set; Anyway; Both of us -- The wilderness: Fallen eagle; Jesus gave love away for free; Colorado; So begins the task; Hide it so deep; Don't look at my shadow -- Consider: It doesn't matter; Johnny's garden; Bound to fall; How far?; Move around; The love gangster -- Rock & roll is here to stay: What to do; Right now; The treasure; Blues man.
    - Steppenwolf: At Your Birthday Party, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0315)
      This album includes Don't cry -- Chicken wolf -- Lovely meter -- Round and down -- It's never too late -- Sleeping dreaming -- Jupiter child -- She'll be better -- Cat killer -- Rock me -- God fearing man -- Mango juice -- Happy birthday.
    - Early Steppenwolf: Recording Live, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0316)
      This album includes Power play -- Howlin' for my baby -- Goin' upstairs -- Corina, Corina -- Tighten up your wig -- The pusher.
    - Steppenwolf: Monster, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0317)
      This album includes Monster; Suicide; America -- Draft resister -- Power play -- Move over -- Fag -- What would you do -- From here to eventually.
    - Cat Stevens: Greatest Hits, 1975 (Record HAMM POP 0318)
      This album includes Wild world (3:19) -- Oh very young (2:35) -- Can't keep it in (2:59) -- Hard headed woman (3:47) -- Moonshadow (2:48) -- Two fine people (3:32) -- Peace train (3:44) -- Ready (3:13) -- Father & son (3:38) -- Sitting (3:11) -- Morning has broken (3:17) -- Another Saturday night (2:27).
    - Cat Stevens: Tea for the tillerman, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0319)
      This album includes Where do the children play (3:48) -- Hard-headed woman (3:42) -- Wild world (3;:5) -- Sad Lisa (3:39) -- Miles from nowhere (3:30) -- But I might die tonight: from the film Deep end (1:51) -- Longer boats (3:07) -- Into white (3:23) -- On the road to find out (5:07) -- Father & son: from the film Revolussi (3:36) -- Tea for the tillerman (1:00).
    - Sting: Nothing Like the sun, 1987 (Record HAMM POP 0320)
      This album includes The Lazarus heart (4:34) -- Be still my beating heart (5:32) --Englishman in New York (4:25) -- History will teach us nothing (4:58) -- They dance alone (Gueca solo) (7:16) -- Fragile (3:54) -- We'll be together (4:52) -- Straight to my heart (3:54) -- Rock steady (4:27) -- Sister Moon (3:46) --Little wing / Jimi Hendrix (5:04) -- The secret marriage (2:03).
    - Sly and the Family Stone: Stand!, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0321)
      This album includes Stand! -- Don't call me nigger, whitey -- I want to take you higher -- Somebody's watching you -- Sing a simple song -- Everyday people -- Sex machine -- You can make it if you try.
    - Barbra Streisand: Je m'appelle Barbra, 1966 (Record HAMM POP 0322)
      This album includes Free again -- Autumn leaves -- What now my love -- Ma première chanson -- Clopin clopant -- Le mur -- I wish you love -- Speak to me of love -- Love and learn -- Once upon a summertime -- Martina -- I've been here.
    - Barbra Streisand: Songbird, 1978 (Record HAMM POP 0323)
      This album includes Tomorrow -- A man I loved -- I don't break easily -- Love breakdown -- You don't bring me flowers -- Honey can I put on your clothes -- One more night -- Stay away -- Deep in the night -- Songbird.
    - Barbra Streisand: The Way We Were, 1974 (Record HAMM POP 0324)
      This album includes Being at war with each other.--Something so right.--The best thing you've ever done.--The way we were.--All in love is fair.--What are you doing the rest of your life.--Summer me, winter me.--Pieces of dreams.--I've never been a woman before.--Medley: My buddy/How about me.
    - Donna Summer: On the Radio (Greatest Hits I & II), 1979 (Record HAMM POP 0325)
      This album includes On the radio / G. Moroder, D. Summer (4:00) -- Love to love you baby / G. Moroder, P. Bellotte, D. Summer (4:07) -- Try me, I know we can make it / D. Summer, G. Moroder, P. Bellotte (3:24) -- I feel love / D. Summer, G. Moroder, P. Bellotte (3:20) -- Our love / D. Summer, G. Moroder (3:43) -- I remember yesterday / D. Summer, G. Moroder, P. Bellotte (4:46) -- I love you / D. Summer, B. Moroder, P. Bellotte (3:12) -- Heaven knows / D. Summer ... [et al.] (3:30) -- Last dance / Paul Jabara (4:56) -- Mac Arthur Park / J.L. Webb (3:54) -- Hot stuff / P. Bellotte, H. Faltermeyer, K. Forsey (2:54) -- Bad girls / D. Summer ... [et al.] (3:05) -- Dim all the lights / D. Summer (4:11) -- Sunset people / P. Bellotte, H. Faltermeyer, K. Forsey (4:32) -- Enough is enough (No more tears) / P. Jabara, B. Roberts (duet with Barbra Streisand) (11:44) -- On the radio / G. Moroder, D. Summer (5:46).
    - Sun City, 1985 (Record HAMM POP 0326)
      This album includes Sun City -- No more apartheid -- Revolutionary situation -- Sun City (version II) -- Let me see your I.D. -- The struggle continues -- Silver and gold.
    - Sun Ra: It's After the End of the World, 1972 (Record HAMM POP 0327)
      This album includes Strange dreams - strange worlds - Black myth; It's after the end of the world -- Black Forest myth -- Watusi, egyptian march -- Myth versus reality (the myth-science approach); Angelic proclamation; Out in space -- Duos.
    - The Supremes: I Hear a Symphony, 1966 (Record HAMM POP 0328)
      This album includes Stranger in paradise -- Yesterday -- I hear a symphony -- Unchained melody -- With a song in my heart -- Without a song -- My world is empty without you -- A lover's concerto -- Any girl in love (knows what I'm going through) -- Wonderful, wonderful -- Everything is good about you -- He's all I got.
    - Ssssh: Ten Years After, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0329)
      This album includes Bad scene (Lee - 3:20) - Two Time Mama (Lee 2:05) - Stoned woman (Lee - #:25) - Good Morning Little School Girl (Williamson - 6:34) - If You should Love Me (Lee - 5:25) - I Don't Know That You Don't Know My Name (Lee - 1:56) - The Stomp (Lee - 4:34) - I Woke Up This Morning (Lee - 5:21).
    - Sweet Honey in the Rock: Good News, 1981 (Record HAMM POP 0330)
      This album includes Breaths.--Echo.--Chile your waters run red through Soweto.--Oh death.--Good news.--Biko.--If you had lived.--Oughta be a woman.--On children.--Time on my hands.--Alla that's all right, but.--Sometime.
    - Taco: After Eight, 1982 (Record HAMM POP 0331)
      This album includes Singin' in the rain -- Tribute to Tino -- Puttin' on the Ritz -- I should care -- Carmella -- La vie en rose -- Cheek to cheek -- After eight -- Livin' in my dreamworld -- Encore (Sweet Gipsy Rose) -- Thanks a million.
    - Talking Heads: Fear of Music, 1979 (Record HAMM POP 0332)
      This album includes I zimbra -- Mind -- Paper -- Cities -- Life during wartime --Memories can't wait -- Air -- Heaven -- Animals -- Electric guitar -- Drugs.
    - Talking Heads: Little Creatures, 1985 (Record HAMM POP 0333)
      This album includes And she was (3:36) -- Give me back my name (3:20) -- Creatures of love (4:12) -- The lady don't mind (4:03) -- Perfect world (4:26) -- Stay up late (3:51) -- Walk it down (4:42) -- Television man (6:10) -- Road to nowhere (4:19).
    - Talking Heads: Naked, 1988 (Record HAMM POP 0334)
      This album includes Blind -- Mr. Jones -- Totally nude -- Ruby dear -- (Nothing but) Flowers -- The democratic circus -- The facts of life -- Mommy Daddy you and I -- Big daddy -- Bill -- Cool water.
    - Talking Heads: The Lady Don't Mind, 1985 (Record HAMM POP 0335)
      This album includes The Lady don't Mind (Extended Mix) (6:46) - Give Me Back My Name (3:19).
    - James Taylor: One Man Dog, 1972 (Record HAMM POP 0336)
      This album includes One man parade -- Nobody but you -- Chili dog -- Fool for you --Instrumental I -- New tune -- Back on the street again -- Don't let me be lonely tonight -- Woh, don't you know -- One morning in May -- Instrumental II -- Someone -- Hymn -- Fanfare -- Little David -- Mescalito -- Dance -- Jig.
    - James Taylor: Sweet Baby James, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0337)
      This album includes Sweet Baby James -- Lo and behold -- Sunny skies -- Steamroller -- Country road -- Oh, Susanna -- Fire and rain -- Blossom -- Anywhere like heaven -- Oh baby, don't you loose your lip on me -- Suite for 20 G.
    - Ten Years After: Cricklewood Green, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0338)
      This album includes Sugar the road -- Working on the road -- 50,000 miles beneath my brain -- Year 3,000 blues -- Me and my baby -- Love like a man -- Circles -- As the sun still burns away.
    - The 1910 Fruitgum Company: Hard Ride, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0339)
      This album includes Don't have to run and hide (2:58) - All these things (2:38) - Beggars' epitaph (3:50) - (a) Eulogy (2:00); (b) Seulb (7:21) - The train (2:300 - Creations of Simon (3:40) - Collections of thoughts (5:08) - (a) In the beginning (1:30); (b) The thing (3:40) - Together alone (5 Movements) (5:30).
    - The Motown Story, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0340)
      This album includes Intro (Berry Gordy Jr.) -- Money (That's what I want) (Barrett Strong) -- Shop around (Smokey Robinson & The Miracles) -- Please Mr. Postman (The Marvelettes) -- Playboy (The Marvelettes) -- Stubborn kind of fellow (Marvin Gaye) -- You've really got a hold on me (Smokey Robinson & The Miracles) -- Pride and joy (Marvin Gaye) -- Finger tips (Stevie Wonder) -- Come and get these memories (Martha Reeves & The Vandellas) -- Mickey's monkey (Smokey Robinson & The Miracles) -- Can I get a witness (Marvin Gaye) -- My guy (Mary Wells) -- Where did our love go (Diana Ross & The Supremes) -- Dancing in the street (Martha Reeves & The Vandellas)
      Baby I need your loving (The Four Tops) -- Baby love (Diana Ross & The Supremes) -- Come see about me (Diana Ross & The Supremes) -- How sweet it is (to be loved by you) (Marvin Gaye) -- My girl (The Temptations) -- Shotgun (Jr. Walker & The All Stars) -- Stop! In the name of love (Diana Ross & The Supremes) -- I'll be doggone (Marvin Gaye) -- Back in my arms again (Diana Ross & The Supremes) -- I can't help myself (The Four Tops) -- The tracks of my tears (Smokey Robinson & The Miracles) -- Nothing but heartaches (Diana Ross & The Supremes) -- I hear a symphony (Diana Ross & The Supremes) -- Uptight (everything's alright) (Stevie Wonder) -- My world is empty without you (Diana Ross & The Supremes)
      My baby loves me (Martha Reeves & The Vandellas) -- Ain't too proud to beg (The Temptations) -- What becomes of the brokenhearted (Jimmy Ruffin) -- You can't hurry love (Diana Ross & The Supremes) -- Reach out I'll be there (The Four Tops) -- You keep me hangin' on (Diana Ross & The Supremes) -- Standing in the shadows of love (The Four Tops) -- Bernadette (The Four Tops) -- Jimmy Mack (Martha Reeves & The Pips) -- Ain't no mountain high enough (Marvin Gaye & Tammi Terrell) -- I was made to love her (Stevie Wonder) -- Reflections (Diana Ross & The Supremes) -- I heard it through the grapevine (Gladys Knight & The Pips) -- I second that emotion (Smokey Robinson & The Miracles) -- I wish it would rain (The Temptations) -- Love child (Diana Ross & The Supremes) -- For once in my life (Stevie Wonder) -- Cloud nine (The Temptations) -- I'm gonna make you love me (Diana Ross & The Supremes & The Temptations) -- I heard it through the grapevine (Marvin Gaye) -- What does it take (to win your love) (Jr. Walker & The All Stars) -- Baby, I'm for real (The Originals) -- I want you back (Jackson 5) -- Psychedelic shack (The Temptations) -- Someday we'll be together (Diana Ross & The Supremes) -- Up the ladder to the roof (The Supremes) -- Reach out and touch (somebody's hand) (Diana Ross) -- Ain't no mountain high enough (Diana Ross).
    - The United States of America (Record HAMM POP 0341)
      This album includes The American Metaphysical Circus (4:55) - Hard Coming Love (4:43) - Cloud Song (3:18) - The Garden of Earthly Delights (2:39) - I Won't Leave My Wooden Wife for You, Sugar (3:52) - Where is Yesterday 93:07) - Coming Down (2:40) - Love Song for the Dead Che (3:25) - Stranded in Time (1:50) - The American Way of Love: 1-Metaphor for an Older Man; II-California Good-Time Music (inspired by Tom Nolan); III-Love is All (6:38).
    - Three Dog Night: One, 1968 (Record HAMM POP 0342)
      This album includes One -- Nobody -- Heaven is in your mind -- It's for you -- Let me go -- Chest fever -- Find someone to love -- That no one ever hurt this bad -- Don't make promises -- The loner -- Try a little tenderness.
    - Three Dog Night: Suitable for Framing, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0343)
      This album includes Feeling alright -- Lady Samantha -- Dreaming isn't good for you -- A change is gonna come -- Eli's coming -- Easy to be hard -- Ain't that a lotta love -- King Soloman's mines -- Circle for a landing -- Celebrate.
    - Traffic: John Barleycorn Must Die, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0344)
      This album includes Glad / Winwood (6:32) -- Freedom rider (6:20); Empty pages (4:47); Stranger to himself (4:02) / Winwood, Capaldi -- John Barleycorn / trad.; arr. Winwood (6:20) -- Every mother's son / Winwood, Capaldi (7:05).
    - Steve Vai's Flexible, 1984 (Record HAMM POP 0345)
      This album includes Little green men -- Viv woman -- Lovers are crazy -- Salamanders in the sun -- The boy/girl song -- The attitude song -- Call it sleep -- Junkie -- Bill's private parts -- Next stop Earth -- There's something dead in here.
    - Sarah Vaughan: Great Hits from the Hit Shows (Vol. 1) (Record HAMM POP 0346)
      This album includes A tree in the park (Peggy Ann -1926) - Little girl blue (Jumbo -1935) - Comes love (Yokel Boy -1939) - But not for me (Girl Crazy -1930) - My darling, my darling (Where's Charley -1948) - Lucky in love (Good News -1927) - Autumn in New York (Thumbs Up -1934) - It never entered my mind (Higher and Higher -1940) - If this isn't love (Finian's Rainbow -1947) - The touch of your hand (Roberta -1933) - Homework (Miss Liberty -1949) - Bewitched (Pal Joey -1940).
    - Suzanne Vega: Solitude Standing, 1987 (Record HAMM POP 0347)
      This album includes Tom's diner -- Luka -- Ironbound/Fancy poultry -- In the eye -- Night vision -- Solitude standing -- Calypso -- Language -- Gypsy -- Wooden horse (Caspar Hauser's song) -- Tom's diner (reprise).
    - The Velvet Underground: Loaded, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0348)
      This album includes Who loves the sun (2:50) -- Sweet Jane (3:55) -- Rock & roll (4:47) -- Cool it down (3:05) -- New age (5:20) -- Head held high (2:52) -- Lonesome cowboy Bill (2:48) -- I found a reason (4:15) -- Train round the bend (3:20) -- Oh! sweet nuthin' (7:23).
    - The Velvet Underground & Nico, 1967 (Record HAMM POP 0349)
      This album includes Sunday Morning (2:53) - I'm waiting for the man (4:37) - Femme Fatale (2:35) - Venus in furs (5:07) - Run Run Run (4:18) - All tomorrow's parties (5:55) - Heroin (7:05) - There she goes again (2:30) - I'll be your mirror (2:01) - The black angel's death song (3:10) - European son to Delmore Schwartz(7:40).
    - The Velvet Underground: White Light/White Heat, 1968 (Record HAMM POP 0350)
      This album includes White light/white heat -- The gift -- Lady Godiva's operation -- Here she comes now -- I heard her call my name -- Sister Ray.
    - Tom Waits: Frank's Wild Years, 1987 (Record HAMM POP 0351)
      This album includes Hang on St. Christopher -- Straight to the top (Rhumba) -- Blow wind blow -- Temptation -- Innocent when you dream (Barroom) -- I'll be gone -- Yesterday is here -- Please wake me up -- Franks theme -- More than rain -- Way down in the hole -- Straight to the top (Vegas) -- I'll take New York -- Telephone call from Istanbul -- Cold cold ground -- Train song -- Innocent when you dream.
    - Tom Waits: Rain Dogs, 1985 (Record HAMM POP 0352)
      This album includes Rain dogs -- Midtown -- 9th and Hennepin -- Gun street girl -- Union square -- Blind love -- Walking Spanish -- Downtown train -- Bride fo rain dog -- Anywhere I lay my head -- Singapore -- Clap hands -- Cemetery polka -- Jockey full of bourbon -- Tango till they're sore -- Big black mariah -- Diamonds and gold -- Hang down your head -- Time.
    - Rick Wakeman: Journey to the Center of the Earth, 1974 (Record HAMM POP 0353)
      This album includes The Journey -- Recollection -- The battle -- The forest.
    - Dionne, 1976 (Record HAMM POP 0354)
      This album includes This girl's in love with you - I'll never fall in love again - Alife - do you know the way to San Jose - Don't make me over - Always something there to remind me - Walk on by - I say a little prayer - Anyone who had a heart - You'll never get to heaven - Windows of the world - Promises, promises - Vally of the dolls - Message to Michael - Trains and boats and planes - Reach out for me - Make it easy on yourself - Odds adn ends - You've lost that lovin' feeling - A house is not a home - April fools - Who is gonna love me - The green grass starts to grow - Let me go to him.
    - Dionne Warwick's Golden Hits, 1968 (Record HAMM POP 0355)
      This album includes What the world needs is love (3:14) - Message to Michael (3:08) - Are you there with another girl (2:500 - I Just don't know what to do with myself (2:50) - Do you know the way to San Jose (2:50) - I say a little prayer for you (3:04) - Who can I turn to (3:05) - Unchained melody (4:12) - Forever my love (2:16) - Trains, Boats and Planes (2:46) - In between heartaches (2:50) - Windows of the world (3:17).
    - Dionne Warwick: Soulful, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0356)
      This album includes You've lost that lovin' feeling -- I'm your puppet -- People got to be free -- You're all I need to get by -- We can work it out -- A hard day's night -- Do right woman, do right man -- I've been loving you too long -- People get ready -- Hey Jude.
    - The Dionne Warwick Story, 1960-1970 (Record HAMM POP 0357)
      This album includes I'm putting me in your hands (2:38) -- Don't make me over (2:08) -- Reach out for me (2:39) -- You'll never get to heaven (3:08) -- Wives and lovers (3:50) -- I just don't know what to do with myself (2:48) -- Anyone who had a heart (2:35) -- Oh yeah yeah yeah (4:00) -- A house is not a home (3:01) -- What'd I say (2:53) -- You and the night and the music (3:07) -- You're gonna hear from me (3:57) -- Taking a chance on love (1:55) -- Try to remember (2:48) -- Medley: Thank heaven for little girls; Walk on by; Message to Michael (6:53) -- Somewhere (3:26) -- Who can I turn to (3:21) -- What's good about goodbye (2:34).; I say a little prayer (2:47) -- For once in my life (3:38) -- The look of love (2:37) -- Going out of my head (2:49) -- Medley: Impossible dream; What the world needs now (4:04) -- Impersonation medley: Baby love; Bill Bailey; Boys in the back room; Falling in love again (4:28) -- Do you know the way to San Jose (2:30) -- Valley of the dolls (3:21) -- Alfie (3:08) -- You made me so very happy (2:41) -- Aquarius (2:26) -- This girl's in love with you (3:31) -- Promises promises (2:38) -- Paper mache (2:47) -- I'll never fall in love again (2:18) -- Make it easy on yourself (3:25) -- Raindrops keep falling on my head (2:41) -- Love medley: Put a little love in your heart; Come together; Get together (6:38).
    - Michael White: The Land of Spirit and Light, 1973 (Record HAMM POP 0358)
      This album includes The land of spirit and light (parts one, two & three) -- Fatima's garden -- Fiesta dominical -- O ancient one -- Lament (Mankind).
    - The Who: Tommy, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0359)
      This album includes Overture; It's a boy -- You didn't hear it -- Amazing journey; Sparks -- Eyesight to the blind -- Christmas -- Cousin Kevin -- The acid queen -- Underture -- Do you think it's alright; Fiddle about -- Pinball wizard -- There's a doctor I've found -- Go to the mirror boy -- Tommy can you hear me -- Smash the mirror -- Sensation -- Miracle cure -- Sally Simpson -- I'm free -- Welcome -- Tommy's holiday camp -- We're not gonna take it.
    - The Winter Consort: Road, 1970-1979 (Record HAMM POP 0360)
      This album includes Icarus (4:30) -- Fantasy, fugue, & ghost beads (7:05) -- Um abraco (4:20) -- Ave Maria Stella; Andromeda (8:14) -- General Pudson's entrance (5:50) -- Come to your senses (6:41) -- Requiem (7:30) -- Africanus Brasileiras (8:10).
    - We are the World, 1985 (Record HAMM POP 0361)
      This album includes We are the world / Michael Jackson & Lionel Richie (USA for Africa) (7:02) -- If only for a moment, girl /Randy Goodrum & S. Perry (Steve Perry) (3:44) -- Just a little closer / Robbie Nevil & Mark Meuller (The Pointer Sisters) (3:53) -- Trapped / Jimmy Cliff (Bruce Springsteen & the E Street Band) (5:11) --Tears are not enough / David Foster (Northern Lights (Canadian All Stars)) (4:21) -- 4 the tears in your eyes / Prince (Prince & the Revolution) (2:45) -- Good for nothing / Richard Marx (Chicago) (3:35) -- Total control / M. Davis & J. Jourard (Tina Turner) (3:38) --A little more love / Tom Schuyler & Fred Knobloch (Kenny Rogers) (2:54) -- Trouble in paradise / Huey Lewis & John Colla (Huey Lewis & the News) (4:34).
    - Stevie Wonder; Characters, 1987 (Record HAMM POP 0362)
      This album includes You will know (5:00) -- Dark 'n' lovely (4:39) -- In your corner (4:30) -- With each beat of my heart (5:28) -- One of a kind (5:10) -- Skeletons (5:24) -- Get it (4:31) -- Galaxy paradise (3:52) -- Cryin' through the night (5:48) -- Free (4:12).
    - WRKO Hall of Fame [1955-1970] (Record HAMM POP 0363)
      This album includes Rock around the clock (Bill Haley & Comets) - The wayward wind (Gogi Grant) - You send me (Sam Cooke) - Silhouettes (The Rays) - It's all in the game (Tommy Edwards) - To know hime is to love him (The Teddy Bears) - Venus (Frankie Avalon) - Kansas City (Wilbert Harrison) - Cathy's clown (The Everly Brothers) - Tossin' & tuening (Bobby Lewis) - Runaway (Del Shannon) - Duke of Earl (Gene Chandler) - Locomotion (Little Eva) - Hey Paula (Paul & Paula) - He's so fine (The Chiffons) - Louie, Louie (The Kingsmen - Wooly Bully (Sam the Sham & the Pharaohs) - Hang on sloopy (The MC Coys) - Cherish (The Association) - Soul & inspiration (The Righteous Brothers) - The letter (The Box Tops) - Happy together (The Turtles) - Harper valley pta (Jeannie C. Riley) - Abraham, Martin & John (Dion) - Smile a little smile for me (The Flying Machine) - Jean (Oliver) - Dizzy (Tommy Roe) - Crystal blue persuation (Tommy James & Shondells) - Venus (The Shocking Blue) - Love on a two-way street (The Moments).
    - Frank Zappa: Hot Rats, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0364)
      This album includes Peaches en regalia (3 min., 58 sec.) -- Willie the pimp (9 min., 25 sec.) -- Son of Mr. Green Genes (8 min., 58 sec.) -- Little umbrellas (3 min., 9 sec.) -- The gumbo variations (12 min., 55 sec.) -- It must be a camel (5 min., 15 sec.).
    - ZZ Top: DeGuello, 1979 (Record HAMM POP 0365)